ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Files /4283/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Lab Safety, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  WNYCOSH, 03C#2824, 05/18/04
- Lead Risk Assessor Refresher [canceled], 2004 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  Public, 03C#2825, 05/18/04, Brown
- Lead Inspector/Risk Assessor [canceled], 2004 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  Public, 03C#2826, 05/17-21/04, Brown
- Indoor Air Quality at Depew M.S., 2004 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  Depew SD, #2827, 06/09/04
- Mental Health in Workplace, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  Cornell Labor Studies, 04C#2828, 01/05
- Gananda S.D.- Indoor Air Quality Tech. Asst., 2004 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2829, 05/27/04
- Occupational Stress, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  NYSUT, 04C#2830, 01/29/05
- Indoor Air Quality Tech. Asst., 2004 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  Sorrento, 03C#2831, 06/21/04
- Trainer's Institute, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  NF ASTD, #2832, 11/12/04
- Stress Mgmt,- Confer Module, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  NYSUT, 04C#2833, 08/20/04
- Hazard Analysis, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  Corning Fiberglass, 04C#2834, 09/13/04
- Hazard Analysis, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  Corning Fiberglass, 04C#2835, 09/14/04
- Vulnerability Analysis, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  NYSEA, 04C#2836, 02/08/05
- S. Davis Elementary- Tech. Asst. (Orchard Park SD), 2004 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2837, 08/19/04
- Multiple Intelligences, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  World Connect, 04C#2838, 08/26/04
- Risk Assessor Refresher [canceled], 2004 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  Public, 04C#2839, 08/26/04, Brown
- Lead Inspector, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  Public, 04C#2840, 09/13-15/04, Brown
- Housing and Urban Development (Proposal), 2004 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  #2841
- Legal Case- Fact Witness, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  Emerson Controls, 04C#2842
- SHRM Module, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  Cornell, 04C#2843, 10/28/04
- Crisis Management (Proposal), 2004 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  NCWA, #2844
- CWA (Proposal), 2004 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  Gordon McClelland, #2845
- Occupational Stress, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  NYSUT, 04C#2846, 10/08/04
- Race- Wegman Fund (Proposed), 2004 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  #2847
- Tools and Techniques Course, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2848, 10-11/2005
- Workplace Hazards and Reg's, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2849, 02/22/05
- Occupational Stress- R.T.A., 2005 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#2850, 09/22/05
- Hazard Evaluation and Control (Chemung County), 2004 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2851, 10/19/04
- Shiftwork Hazards, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2852, 12/07/04
- Health and Safety Committee Skills, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2853
- Indoor Air Quality (BOMA), 2005 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2854, 02/23/05
- Risk Assessor, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  Public, 04C#2855, 9/16-17/04, Brown
- Risk Assessor Refresher [canceled], 2004 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  Public, 04C#2856, 10/21/04, Brown
- Lead Training, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  Monroe County, #2857, 01/05
- Tech. Asst., 2005 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  John Crane Inc., 05C#2858, 10/04-07/05
- Indoor Air Quality Site Investigation- S. Davis Elementary, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2859, 11/08-09/04
- No. 2860: Cornell Program on Breast Cancer and Environmental Risk Factors [Folder 1 of 3], 2008 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- No. 2860: Cornell Program on Breast Cancer and Environmental Risk Factors [Folder 2 of 3], 2008 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- No. 2860: Cornell Program on Breast Cancer and Environmental Risk Factors [Folder 3 of 3], 2008 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Breast Cancer Database Structure, 2006-2008 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  #2860
- Breast Cancer Database Project, 2007-2008 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Cornell Vet. School/BCERF, 2009-2010 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Work plan '09-'10, #2860
- Blood borne Pathogens and Violence for UFCW, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2865, 04/12/05
- Blood borne Pathogens and Violence for UFCW, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2866, 04/20/05
- Friendship Dairy- JHA, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2867, 01/20/05
- Lab Safety, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  Utica National Ins., #2868, 11/11/04
- Environmental Safety Module, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  BOMA, 04C#2869, 01/12/05
- Extension-Resident Collaboration Committee- Seminar, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  #2870, 12/03/04
- Occupational Stress, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  NYSUT, 04C#2871, 01/29/05
- Hazmat Refresher, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 11a)
  IUOE, 04C#2872, 01/31/05
- Hazmat Refresher, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 11b)
  IUOE, 04C#2873, 02/01/05
- Hazmat Refresher, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 11c)
  IUOE, 04C#2874, 02/02/05
- Hazmat Refresher, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 11d)
  IUOE, 04C#2875, 02/03/05
- Hazmat Refresher [Cancelled], 2005 (Box 14, Folder 11e)
  IUOE, 04C#2876, 02/04/05
- Hazmat Refresher, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 11f)
  IUOE, 04C#2877, 02/07/05
- Hazmat Refresher, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 11g)
  IUOE, 04C#2878, 02/08/05
- Hazmat Refresher, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 11h)
  IUOE, 04C#2879, 02/09/05
- SHRM, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  Cornell, 04C#2880, 04/18/05
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 04C#2883, 2/10/05, Brown
- WWTP Hazards for NYWEA, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2881, 06/23/05
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 04C#2882, 01/25/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 04C2884, 2/22/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 04C#2885, 03/10/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 04C#2886, 3/22/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 04C#2887, 04/14/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 04C#2888, 04/26/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 04C#2889, 05/03/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 04C#2890, 5/20/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 04C#2891, 5/21/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 04C#2892, 6/2/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 04C#2893, 06/17/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 04C#2894, 06/18/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#2895, 7/15/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#2896, 7/16/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#2897, 7/26/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#2898, 8/12/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#2899, 8/13/05, Brown,
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#2900, 8/23/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#2901, 9/9/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#2902, 9/10/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#2903, 9/20/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#2905, 10/15/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#2906, 10/25/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#2907, 11/1/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#2908, 11/17/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#2909, 12/1/05, Brown
- Lead Safety for Remodeling, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#2910, 12/15/05, Brown
- Lead Risk Assessor Refresher, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  Public Program, 04C#2911, 2/23/05, Brown
- Greater Buffalo Environmental Conference, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2912, 3/16/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2913, 06/13/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2914, 06/13/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2915, 06/14/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2916, 06/14/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2917, 06/15/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2918, 06/15/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2919, 06/16/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2920, 06/16/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  WNYCOSH, #2921, 06/21/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  WNYCOSH, #2922, 06/21/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  WNYCOSH, #2923, 06/22/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  WNYCOSH, #2924, 06/22/05
- S. Tier Planning Board Conference- Confined Space, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2925, 05/12/05
- Small Scale Composting Factsheet, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  CWMI, #2926
- No. 2927: Agriculture [Folder 1 of 9], 2005-2007 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- No. 2927: Agriculture [Folder 2 of 9], 2005-2007 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- No. 2927: Agriculture [Folder 3 of 9], 2005-2007 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- No. 2927: Agriculture [Folder 4 of 9], 2005-2007 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- No. 2927: Agriculture [Folder 5 of 9], 2005-2007 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- No. 2927: Agriculture [Folder 6 of 9], 2005-2007 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- No. 2927: Agriculture [Folder 7 of 9], 2005-2007 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- No. 2927: Agriculture [Folder 8 of 9], 2005-2007 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- No. 2927: Agriculture [Folder 9 of 9], 2005-2007 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- IBEW- Asbestos Awareness, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  WNYCOSH, 4/28/05, #2928
- Crisis Management, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2929, 05/17/05
- Crisis Management, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2930, 05/18/05
- Lead Inspector, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  US Military Academy, 04C#2931, 3/28-30/05, Brown
- Risk Assessor, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  US Military Academy, 04C#2932, 3/31-4/1/05, Brown
- Lead Inspector, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  NYS Dept. of Health/Public, 04C#2933, 3/14-16/05, Brown
- Risk Assessor, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  NYS Dept. of Health/Public, 04C#2934, 3/17-18/05, Brown
- Confined Space, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  NYSTA, 04C#2935, 4/25/05
- Inspector [canceled], 2005 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  Public, 04C#2936, 4/18-20/05, Brown
- Risk Assessor [canceled], 2005 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  Public, 04C#2937, 4/21-22/05, Brown
- NYS Weatherization Directors (Proposal), 2005 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  #2938
- HazOp- Welch's, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2939, 03/24/05
- HazOp- Welch's, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2940, 03/24/05
- Confined Space- Welch's, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2941, 03/24/05
- Confined Space- Welch's, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  Welch's, 04C#2942, 03/24/05
- Blood Borne Pathogens- Trainer, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  WNYCOSH, #2943, 05/02/05
- Ironworks (Rochester), 2005 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2944, 04/16/05
- No. 2945: Occupational Stress [Folders 1 of 3], 2005-2006 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- No. 2945: Occupational Stress [Folders 2 of 3], 2005-2008 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- No. 2945: Occupational Stress [Folders 3 of 3], 2005-2006 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Water/Wastewater, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  NYWEA, 05C#2946, 10/04/05
- Water/Wastewater, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  NYWEA, 05C#2947, 10/05/05
- Water/Wastewater, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  NYWEA, 05C#2948, 10/06/05
- Jamestown Firefighters [Folders 1-4], 2005 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#2949-52, 07/11-15/05
- MCWA, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2953, 05/13/05
- MCWA, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2954, 05/13/05
- MCWA, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2955, 06/09/05
- Tech Asst.- Indoor Air Quality, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  ASPIRE, 04C#2956, 05/05/05
- HazCom- MCWA, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  WNYCOSH, #2957, 06/09/05
- Indoor Air Quality- ASPIRE, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2958, 05/31/05
- HazCom- MCWA, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  WNYCOSH, #2959, 06/24/05
- HazCom- MCWA, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  WNYCOSH, #2960, 06/24/05
- Critical Issues in Health and Safety, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  Cornell Upstate Labor, #2961, 02/21/06
- SHRM Module, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  Cornell, 04C#2962, 11/22/05
- No. 2963: Extension- Resident Collaboration [Folder 1 of 4], 2005-2007 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- No. 2963: Extension- Resident Collaboration [Folder 2 of 4], 2005-2007 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- No. 2963: Extension- Resident Collaboration [Folder 3 of 4], 2005-2007 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- No. 2963: Extension- Resident Collaboration [Folder 4 of 4], 2005-2007 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Lead Inspector [canceled], 2005 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  Public, 04C#2964, 6/20-22/05, Brown
- Risk Assessor [canceled], 2005 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  Public, 04C#2965, 6/23-24/05, Brown
- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  WNYCOSH, 04C#2966, 06/24/05
- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#2967, 08/11/05
- Tech Asst.- Indoor Air Quality, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  Amherst S.D., 05C#2968, 07/12/05
- Lead Inspector Initial [canceled], 2005 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  Public Program, 05C#2969, 9/26-28/05, Brown
- Risk Assessor Initial [canceled], 2005 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  Public Program, 05C#2970, 9/29-30/05, Brown
- Risk Assessor Refresher [canceled], 2005 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  Public Program, 05C#2971, 7/13/05, Brown
- Risk Assessor Refresher [canceled], 2005 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  Public Program, 05C#2972, 7/27/05, Brown
- Tech. Asst., 2005 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  ASPIRE, 05C#2973, 07/07/05
- Tech. Asst., 2005 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  WNYCOSH, #2974
- Conference- Composing Health and Safety Issues, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  NYWEA, 05C#2975, 02/07/05
- Shiftwork (Proposal), 2005 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  NYSDOT, #2977
- Risk Assessor Refresher, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  Public, 05C#2978, 8/11/05, Brown
- Risk Assessor Refresher, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  Public, 05C#2980, 9/7/05, Brown
- Trainer, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  Owens-Corning, 05C#2979, 11/8-9/05
- UFCW- Sexual Harassment, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  WNYCOSH, 04/05/06, 05C#2981
- UFCW, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#2982, 04/19/06
- World Connect, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  #2983, 08/25/05
- Stress, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  IAAP, 05C#2984, 02/01/06
- Tech. Asst., 2005 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  TREK, #2985
- Lead Worker Training, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  Public Program, 05C#2986, 7/28-29/05, Brown
- Custodians- Workplace Violence, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#2987, 10/11/05
- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#2988, 11/16/05
- BMHA- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#2989, 01/10/06
- BMHA- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#2990, 01/10/06
- BMHA- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#2991, 01/11/06
- BMHA- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#2992, 01/11/06
- BMHA- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#2993, 01/17/06
- BMHA- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#2994, 01/17/06
- BMHA- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#2995, 01/18/06
- BMHA- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#2996, 01/18/06
- BMHA- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#2997, 01/24/06
- Mammary Carcinogens- Scenarios and Panel Discussion, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  Cornell BCERF, 05C#2998, 06/02/06
- Stress, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#2999, 03/27/06
- Vulnerability Analysis, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  CMED, 06C#3000, 11/20/06
- Confined Space/LOTO (NYWEA Webcast), 2006 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  WNYCOSH, #3002, 06/28/06
- Ridgeline Farm, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  Cornell Manure Mgmt., #3004
- Blood Borne Pathogens- Firefighters, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  WNYCOSH, #3003, 07/26/06
- (Paterson Farm- Digester) Confined Space and Chemical Hazards, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3005, 11/18/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3006, 10/24/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3007, 10/24/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3008, 10/25/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3009, 10/25/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3010, 10/26/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3011, 10/26/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3012, 10/27/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3013, 10/27/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3014, 10/28/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3015, 10/28/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3016, 10/31/05
- City of Buffalo, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3017, 10/31/05
- Indoor Air Quality, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  Cornell Mgmt., #3018, 05/18/06
- Cosmetology Module of Conference, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3019, 10/22/05
- Lewiston WWTP, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3020, 12/14/05
- Lewiston WWTP, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3021, 12/15/06
- Labor Law II- OSHA, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  Cornell Labor Studies, 05C#3022, 05/11/06
- Reg. Cancer and Env. Forum, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  Cornell BCERF, 05C#3023, 09/30/05
- Indoor Air Quality Tech. Asst., 2005 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  ASPIRE, 05C#3024, 09/26/05
- Hazmat Refresher [Folders 1-6], 2006 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  IUOE, 05C#3025-3030, 2/02-17/06
- Disaster Site Worker [canceled], 2006 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  IUOE, 05C#3031, 02/20/06
- Disaster Site Worker, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  IUOE, 05C#3032, 02/23/06
- Disaster Site Worker, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  IUOE, 05C#3033, 02/27/06
- No. 3034: Cornell Waste Management Institute [Folder 1 of 4], 2008 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- No. 3034: Cornell Waste Management Institute [Folder 2 of 4], 2008 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- No. 3034: Cornell Waste Management Institute [Folder 3 of 4], 2008 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- No. 3034: Cornell Waste Management Institute [Folder 4 of 4], 2008 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Hazard Analysis Techniques, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  CUTCO (ALCAST), 05C#3035, 03/15/06
- Lead Inspector Initial, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  Public, 05C#3036, 11/7-9/05, Brown
- Risk Assessor Initial, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  Public, 05C#3037, 11/10-11/05, Brown
- Occupational Stress- RTA, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3038, 11/01/05
- Indoor Air Quality, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3039, 11/17/05
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#3040, 1/24/06, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#3041, 2/14/06, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#3042, 3/7/06, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#3043, 3/21/06, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#3044, 4/11/06, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#3045, 4/25/06, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#3046, 5/9/06, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#3047, 5/23/06, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#3048, 6/8/06, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 05C#3049, 6/20/06, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3052, 8/4/06, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3050, 7/11/06, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3051, 7/25/06, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3053, 8/22/06, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3054, 9/5/06, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3055, 9/19/06, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3056, 10/03/06, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3057, 10/17/06, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3059, 11/14/06, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3058, 11/2/06, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3060, 12/05/06, Brown
- Lead Inspector Refresher, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  Adelaide LLC, 05C#3061, 10/28/05, Brown
- Lead Risk Assessor Refresher [canceled], 2005 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  Public, 05C#3062, 12/2/05, Brown
- Lead Training (Proposal), 2005 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  NYCHPD, #3063
- Composting Health and Safety, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  Kansas Dept. of Health and Safety, 05C#3064, 03/28-29/06
- SHRM Module (Occ. Health and Safety), 2006 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  Cornell, #3065, 04/19/06
- HAZOP- NYSTA, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3066, 05/03/06
- G.B.E.C., 2006 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3067, 03/21/06
- Hazard Analysis, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  Owens-Corning, D6C#3068, 04/24-25/07
- Risk Assessor Refresher, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  Public, 05C#3069, 1/25/06, Brown
- Risk Assessor Refresher, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  Public, 05C#3070, 2/13/06, Brown
- Training- Generic Digester Protocol, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  Cornell Manure Management, 05C#3071, 1/23/06
- Indoor Air Quality Tech. Asst., 2005 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  Gundersen, #3072, 12/02/05
- Respiratory Protection, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  MCWA, #3073, 12/16/05
- Interest-Based for Health and Safety, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3074, 02/18/06
- Process Hazards Analysis, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  NRG, #3080; contains newspaper clips
- Lead Inspector, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  Public, 05C#3075, 2/28-3/1/06, Brown
- Risk Assessor, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  Public, 05C#3076, 3/2-3/06, Brown
- Supervisor Contractor Refresher, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  Chautauqua Home Rehab and Improvement, 05C#3077, 1/26/05, Brown
- Worker Refresher, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  Chautauqua Home Rehab and Improvement, 05C#3078, 1/27/05, Brown
- "Tools for Schools", 2006 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  WNYCOSH, 05C#3081, 03/23/06
- Lead Remodelers, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  SUNY at Brockport, 05C#3082, 3/22/06, Brown
- Lead Inspector, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  Public, 05C#3083, 3/27-29/06, Brown
- Risk Assessor Refresher, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  Public, 05C#3085, 4/6/06, Brown
- Lead Risk Assessor, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  Public, 05C#3084, 3/30-31/06, Brown
- Hazard Analysis Techniques, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  Cutco (ALCAST), 05C#3086
- Hazard Analysis Techniques, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  CUTCO (ALCAST), 05C#3087
- Hazard Analysis Techniques, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  CUTCO (ALCAST), 05C#3088